# STACK

- React JS
- Typescript
- Tailwind CSS
- Javascript
- PHP Laravel
- VUE JS
- Redux JS
- SASS
- Node JS
- PostgreSQL
- Express
- Scrum (JIRA)

I am a programmer with strong soft skills, excelling in communication, teamwork, adaptability to changes, leadership, self-learning, and more. I have a solid experience in HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Tailwind, and ReactJS, specializing in front-end web development and creating high performance interactive interfaces

# CONTACT



<u>Portfolio</u>



+57 3212159041



edwar.leon.m@gmail.com



<u>LinkedIn</u>

# **SOFT SKILLS**

Leadership

Communication

Adaptability to changes

Self-learning

Teamwork

# **LANGUAGES**

English B1

Native Spanish

# **LEÓN** EDWAR

# **FULL STACK DEVELOPER**

# **EDUCATION**

#### **MAY 2023 - PRESENT**

#### Full Stack Web Developer - Academio

Outstanding student in the fundamentals and React JS modules, creating projects with solid foundations in full stacks. Link here.

### **APRIL 2022 - SEPTEMBER 2022**

# WEB DEVELOPER - Alura (ONE)

Link here.

# **EXPERIENCE**

**NOVEMBER 2023 - CURRENT** 

Kaba Clubs

#### **TECHNICAL LEAD- FRONTEND DEV**

Leading a multifunctional team to craft innovative solutions. Implementing agile methodologies, streamlining processes, and steering successful projects, showcasing superior technical and managerial skills. Programming and designing the views of the vendor portal.

# AUGUST 2023 - JANUARY 2024 Linde

#### LOGISTICS COORDINATOR

Ensuring national transportation of vehicles carrying vital gases such as Argon, Oxygen, CO2, and Nitrogen for food companies and hospitals. Supervising drivers' schedules and satellite tracking of vehicles, ensuring precise deliveries.

# **APRIL 2022 - FEBRUARY 2023**

IBM OPERATIONS SUPERVISOR

Atlantic QI

- Leading a team of 40 BackOffice agents for the IBM campaign.
- Reporting on results.
- KPIs (Key Performance Indicators).
- Quality indicators.
- Reporting delivery.
- Increasing BackOffice management from 12 to 60 tasks.
- Increasing quality indicator from 45% to 85%.

# AUGUST 2015 - DECEMBER 2021 ) Innovacryl - LD

# **ADMINISTRATOR**

- Managing and handling websites.
- Web page layout.
- Web page design and development.

# **PROJECTS**

# **E-COMMERCE - PORTAL USUARIOS**

- Purchase and service procurement registration and control application for Kaba Clubs e-commerce, managing refunds, purchasing processes, and more.
- For this project, we utilized React.js, Tailwind CSS, Redux.js, Git, API consumption, and Laravel.

# **POKEDEX**

- Web application for searching Pokémon and accessing their abilities and statistics.
- This project utilized React Js, Tailwind, Redux Js, Git, and API consumption.
- Repository link, Project link

# **RICK AND MORTY APP**

- Web application for searching characters from the series and learning about their origin and status.
- This project employed React Js, Tailwind, Redux Js, Git, and API consumption.
- Repository link, Project link